jdmagicbox.com 2014-07-15

# Privacy Policy – Justdial US

Login Sign Up  [](http://us.justdial.com/) [](http://us.justdial.com/) New York, NY  [National Search](http://us.justdial.com/allus)  Remember My Location 

###  Privacy Policy

**Policy:** This Privacy Policy (" **Policy** ") describes the manner in which (" **Just Dial** " or " **We** / **Us** / **Our** ") treat personal information that you may provide to us, while using our services. We respect your privacy. 

**Information with US:** We offer a number of search related services. We will have access to certain information about you on account of your use of the services. We may also have access to certain other information including personal information about you. The Policy sets forth the manner in which we will deal with all such information. Both categories of information are referred to as " **Information** "). 

**Information you provide:** We ask you to provide information to us in order to provide certain services. Such information may include personal information such as your name, e-mail address, phone number, home address, services / products that you require etc. You are at liberty to decide whether you want to provide such information to us. If you choose not to provide all or portion of such information, we may not be able to provide some or all of the services that you require. We also record voice calls and store the same for internal purposes including quality control, improving our services etc. 

**Use of Information:** We will use the Information in order to provide services to you. In the course of performing the services, we may need to provide some or all of Information to third parties. You agree that you have no objection to such disclosure. At your request, we may also provide your phone number, email id and address to vendors and service providers in order that may be get in touch with you. We may use Information for various internal purposes including for (a) improving our services, (b) creating new offerings, (c) protecting Our rights, (d) protecting third party rights including other users of services. We may aggregate non-personal information about the users of Our services / persons who visit Our websites and share the same with any third parties on such terms as may be deemed appropriate. For instance, we may share information about the number of users who asked for information about a particular service or information about the number of users who purchased certain categories of products or information in a particular area etc. 

**Other Uses:** We may send cookies to you from our websites. These cookies generally improve the quality of our services to you. We / Our service provider servers record information that your browser sends when you visit our websites. Please remember that your browsers are set up to provide information to Us / Our service providers. You can disable such features. If you do disable such features, please remember that some of the services may not be effective. Reviews that you may post on our websites and communications that you may make to us will be retained by us and generally used for the purpose of improving our services. 

**Disclosure of Information:** We share information that you provide including personal information and other information that is available with us under the following circumstances: We believe in good faith that sharing information is necessary (a) to satisfy applicable law, rules or regulations, (b) to comply with any judicial or regulatory request or order, (c) detect or prevent any fraud or violation of an obligations that are owed by you, (d) protect ourselves and other third parties including our users from any loss or damage or to prevent any damage to any property. You have consented to sharing information. Sharing information is necessary in order to provide the services. We outsource the performance of various functions to third parties, which may include technology related services, hosting servers etc. Our vendors and service providers may have access to Information. Please note that some of such servers may be located outside the country you are in. You confirm and agree that you have no objection to the same. 

**Links:** The Policy applies only in respect of information provided to Us / your access to Our websites. It does not apply to any websites that you may access from the links provided on our websites. 

**Third Parties:** We may, as discussed above, provide Information to third parties. While the third parties are bound by appropriate confidentiality obligations, we cannot guarantee that they will not misuse the Information and we will not be liable for any such misuse by them. 

**Security:** We take reasonable measures to ensure that there is no unauthorized access to servers where Information is stored. Please remember that we cannot guarantee that no breach of security will occur. 

**Communications:** We encourage you to write to us about any privacy concerns. You may have including concerns about the Policy. You may write (a) to or email at (b) : Just Dial Global Pvt Ltd (Includes its Affiliates and subsidiaries), Registered Address: 501 / B, Palm Court Complex, New Link Road, Malad (W), Mumbai 400 064 India. You can send us the email at: [privacy.us@justdial.com](mailto:privacy.us@justdial.com)

**Changes to this Privacy Policy:** The Policy may change from time to time. The Policy as amended will be posted on [www.justdial.com](http://us.justdial.com/) and upon such posting will be binding on you. If the changes are not acceptable to you, please write to us at the address provided above and we will delete all Information from our systems. 

**Assignment:** If Just Dial is merged with any other entity or Just Dial's business is acquired by any other entity, the buyer / merged entity will be contractually bound by the Policy and any changes they may make will be subject to the terms of the Policy. 

**User's Reponsibility for its Information:** The user acknowledges that they shall be solely responsible and liable for the authenticity and genuineness of their information, they provide to Just Dial while using the Just Dial service/s. The User confirms that it will provide the correct information about itself. In the event the user provides any wrong or incomplete information, then the user alone shall be liable and responsible for the same.. Further, user also acknowledges that the information provided by the user is voluntarily. 

**Updation of User Information:** The User acknowledges and accepts that, the user will regularly and from time to time update its (user) information. 

**Legal Age of the User:** It is presumed that the user, using the Just Dial service is of Legal Age. In the event the user is not of a Legal age, then any issues or problems arising out of using Just Dial Service/s, which requires a user to be of Legal age, then Just Dial shall not be responsible for any such issues or problems. The aforementioned Privacy Policy (" **Policy** " is for the US based User of Just Dial ) describes the manner in which Just Dial Global Pvt Ltd ((Includes its Affiliates and subsidiaries), a company incorporated under the laws of India, and having its principal place of business at 501 / B, Palm Court Complex, New Link Road, Malad (W), Mumbai 400 064 India)), treats the personal information that you may provide to us, while using our services. 

[ Free Listing ](http://us.justdial.com/advertise.php?f=1 "Free Business Listing on Justdial") [ Share your views about Justdial ](http://us.justdial.com/cms/index.php?option=com_testimonialku&Itemid=45#testimonialform "Share your views about Justdial") [ Advertise ](http://us.justdial.com/advertise.php?f=2 "Advertise on Justdial") X

Email

Password

X Sign In **OR** Sign in with your JD account

Email / Phone

Password

X

### Your Feedback for Justdial

X

### Thanks for Your Feedback!

X New User Signup

Salutation

First Name *

Last Name *

Mobile *

Email Address *

Password *

Re-type Password *

X

What is Just Dial Verified? Just Dial Verified(JD Verified) is an added services offering.

Justdial verified means that the information of business establishments, professionals or service providers has been verified as existing and correct at the time of the advertiser's application to register with Justdial. 

Benefits of using JD Verified Makes short-listing of business establishments, professionals or service providers fast & easy. Information verification time is saved. 

(PS: There is no documentary evidence gathered for verification)  
If you need any more details on Justdial Verified, please refer to [terms & conditions](http://us.justdial.com/terms-of-use)

X Forgot Your Password

Please enter your login email

Enter the code as displayed in the image below (not case-sensitive)

X

'Reviews & Ratings' are given by Justdial Users, who have experienced the services of the various businesses listed on Justdial.

Be it restaurants, hotels, product dealers, service providers, professionals or just about anything. 

You could also share your experience and help others make a suitable choice. 

Go ahead find the listing and share your experience, this can help someone.  X

Mobile Verification

We have sent you a Verification Code by SMS. To complete sign-up please enter the verification code here-

Thank You

X X X

**Critics Rating**

Critics rating is an average of top 5 media critics of  
the country

X

**JD User Ratings**

Ratings are given by users of Justdial.com based on their personal experience about the movie
